<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>San Francisco Critical Mass on SF Critical Mass</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/</link><description>Recent content in San Francisco Critical Mass on SF Critical Mass</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Contributors, MIT License</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 12:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sfcriticalmass.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>July 2022 Ride Recap</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-07-29-recap/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-07-29-recap/</guid><description>The tunnel ride! We set out at around 6:45pm and headed via Market up through both the Stockton and Broadway tunnels with Chinatown in between. Both tunnels were uphill, so we turned around and cruised back down through them. A total of four tunnel traversals in the first half hour! We then continued along a relatively standard route, along Market to Valencia and up to Mission Dolores Park for a rest stop.</description></item><item><title>June 2022 Ride Recap</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-06-24-recap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-06-24-recap/</guid><description>The Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade this Friday June 24, upending 50 years of settled law in a blatant attack on women&amp;rsquo;s and LGBTQ+ rights, sparking protests all across the country and world. San Francisco had at least three separate protests which converged together, as well as the Trans March, leading to a chaotic evening.
Critical Mass set out around 6:50pm as we were waiting for Deep and his music bike Trikeasaurus.</description></item><item><title>May 2022 Ride Recap</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-05-recap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-05-recap/</guid><description>About a hundred people attended Critical Mass this May 27th. We left Embarcadero Plaza at 6:30 pm sharp, headed down Market St to Valencia and up to Dolores Park for the first stop. Local legend Backwards Brian made an appearance but was unfortunately stopped by a flat tire after the first stop.
Rolling down Valencia Street with Backwards Brian. We continued down through the Mission and back around Oracle Park where SFSU&amp;rsquo;s commencement ceremony was taking place for our second stop.</description></item><item><title>April 2022 Ride Recap</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-04-recap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:38:56 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-04-recap/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of this blog, I thought it might be nice to upload recaps
of each month&amp;rsquo;s ride. So here&amp;rsquo;s how the April 29 ride from last week went.
All things considered, the planned route worked better than expected! Many
people peeled off early but a handful of us completely a full 16 mile route
from Embarcadero Plaza to the Greay Walkway in about 3.5 hours.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>April JFK Promenade Route + Reflections</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/jfk-promenade-xerox/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/jfk-promenade-xerox/</guid><description>A Route To Celebrate Car-Free JFK JFK Drive in Golden Gate Park is now permanently car-free! On Tuesday, April 26, the SF Board of Supervisors voted to pass Mayor London Breed&amp;rsquo;s plan, with ammendments to ensure accesibility and equity.
To celebrate, I am proposing a route thru the &amp;ldquo;JFK Promenade&amp;rdquo; which also traverses other important bike routes still requiring serious people-first safety improvements: Market St, Valencia St, The Wiggle, and The Great Walkway.</description></item><item><title>Connect</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/connect/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/connect/</guid><description>SF Critical Mass has no leaders, so every social media profile (and this website!) is unofficial.
SF Critical Mass (Current) Twitter: https://twitter.com/CriticalMassSF Instagram: https://www.instagram.com/sfcriticalmass Facebook Page: https://www.facebook.com/CriticalMassSF GitHub: https://github.com/sfcriticalmass Old SF Critical Mass Twitter: https://twitter.com/sfcriticalmass Facebook Page: https://www.facebook.com/sfcriticalmass Original Blog: https://www.sfcriticalmass.org Other Organizations San Francisco Bike Party: https://sfbikeparty.wordpress.com SafeStreetRebel: https://www.safestreetrebel.com San Francisco Bicycle Coalition: https://sfbike.org</description></item></channel></rss>