<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on SF Critical Mass</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on SF Critical Mass</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Contributors, MIT License</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 17:00:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>August 2022 Ride Recap</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-08-26-recap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Aug 2022 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-08-26-recap/</guid><description>&lt;figure>
 &lt;img src='https://sfcriticalmass.com/images/2022-08-26_market.jpg' alt='Bikes filling up Market St at the Gough intersection.'>
 &lt;figcaption>Market &amp;amp; Gough&lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;p>This was an absolutely fantastic classic ride across the city and back. Thank
you to everyone who came, each ride seems to be bigger than the last as we
approach the 30th anniversary next month. We rode out at 6:45 pm up Market St
and through The Wiggle. With more than enough bikes we took over the Fell
Expressway and continued on to the Golden Gate Park Bandshell Accessible
Parking lot for our first break.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>July 2022 Ride Recap</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-07-29-recap/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Jul 2022 12:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-07-29-recap/</guid><description>&lt;p>The tunnel ride! We set out at around 6:45pm and headed via Market up through
both the Stockton and Broadway tunnels with Chinatown in between. Both tunnels
were uphill, so we turned
around and cruised back down through them. A total of four tunnel traversals
in the first half hour! We then continued along a relatively standard route,
along Market to Valencia and up to Mission Dolores Park for a rest stop.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>June 2022 Ride Recap</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-06-24-recap/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Jun 2022 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-06-24-recap/</guid><description>&lt;p>The Supreme Court overturned Roe v. Wade this Friday June 24, upending 50
years of settled law in a blatant attack on women&amp;rsquo;s and LGBTQ+ rights,
sparking protests all across the country and world. San Francisco had
at least three separate protests which converged together, as well as the
&lt;a href="https://www.transmarch.org/trans-march-2022/">Trans March&lt;/a>, leading to a
chaotic evening.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Critical Mass set out around 6:50pm as we were waiting for
&lt;a href="https://twitter.com/deepasaurus">Deep and his music bike Trikeasaurus&lt;/a>.
We headed up Market Street, where we quickly ran into barriers at 7th Street
for the protests. We continued through Hayes Valley and biked through cars
sitting in traffic on Octavia, Oak, and Fell. Caltrans had closed the entrance
to the normally loud polluting Central Freeway as thousands walked by in the
Trans March. We continued along Market to The Castro, a destination several
people wanted to reach in honor of Pride, and then rode down to Dolores Park
for the first stop.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>May 2022 Ride Recap</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-05-recap/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2022 17:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-05-recap/</guid><description>&lt;p>About a hundred people attended Critical Mass this May 27th. We left
Embarcadero Plaza at 6:30 pm sharp, headed down Market St to Valencia and up to
Dolores Park for the first stop. Local legend &lt;a href="https://www.instagram.com/backwards_brian/">Backwards Brian&lt;/a>
made an appearance but was unfortunately stopped by a flat tire after the first
stop.&lt;/p>
&lt;figure>
 &lt;img src='https://sfcriticalmass.com/images/2022-05-27_valencia.jpg' alt='Rolling down Valencia Street with Backwards Brian.'>
 &lt;figcaption>Rolling down Valencia Street with Backwards Brian.&lt;/figcaption>
&lt;/figure>

&lt;p>We continued down through the Mission and back around Oracle Park where
&lt;a href="https://commencement.sfsu.edu/commencement-2022-may-27-oracle-park-sfsu-grad">SFSU&amp;rsquo;s commencement ceremony&lt;/a>
was taking place for our second stop.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>April 2022 Ride Recap</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-04-recap/</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2022 14:38:56 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/2022-04-recap/</guid><description>&lt;p>As part of this blog, I thought it might be nice to upload recaps
of each month&amp;rsquo;s ride. So here&amp;rsquo;s how the April 29 ride from last week went.
All things considered, the planned route worked better than expected! Many
people peeled off early but a handful of us completely a full 16 mile route
from Embarcadero Plaza to the Greay Walkway in about 3.5 hours.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>April JFK Promenade Route + Reflections</title><link>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/jfk-promenade-xerox/</link><pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2022 09:00:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://sfcriticalmass.com/posts/jfk-promenade-xerox/</guid><description>&lt;h1 id="a-route-to-celebrate-car-free-jfk">A Route To Celebrate Car-Free JFK&lt;/h1>
&lt;p>JFK Drive in Golden Gate Park is now permanently car-free! On Tuesday, April 26,
the SF Board of Supervisors voted to pass Mayor London Breed&amp;rsquo;s plan, with
ammendments to ensure accesibility and equity.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>To celebrate, I am proposing a route thru the &amp;ldquo;JFK Promenade&amp;rdquo; which also
traverses other important bike routes still requiring serious people-first
safety improvements: Market St, Valencia St, The Wiggle, and The Great Walkway.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>